Hrushka Daria

A full-time Product Manager with over 5 years in the IT industry. Specializing in product management, software development, and business analysis. Possesses a unique blend of technical expertise and leadership, with a strong focus on collaboration, problem-solving, and driving continuous

Previously, I was a Dev Team Lead, blending management with hands-on development tasks.

+38 (066) 801-47-53

telegram: @kldasha daria.hrushka@gmail.com

website: portfolio

EXPERIENCE

<u>Interkassa</u>. Payment systems aggregator — *BA to product manager* Kyiv, Ukraine

JULY 2022 - NOWADAYS

As the Product Manager, led the team to a 37% increase in feature development output with improving the SDLC. My role encompassed:

- Product Roadmap: formed and monitored product roadmaps, aligning with market needs and business priorities.
- Requirements Engineering: formed detailed product requirements, ensuring they captured the essence of user needs and business goals.
- Agile: lead and facilitate daily scrums, sprint planning, sprint reviews, and retrospectives
- **Technical Collaboration**: partnered closely with engineering teams, communicating about product vision, and priorities, clarifying tasks, creating spikes, monitoring and managing their implementation.
- **System Architecture**: contributed to the system architecture design, ensuring scalability and alignment with product goals.
- **Performance Metrics**: established and monitored key performance indicators to ensure product effectiveness.
- Customer Engagement: gathered feedback to inform product development and enhance customer satisfaction.
- Backlog management: effectively managed and prioritized the product backlog, ensuring alignment with business goals and stakeholder expectations.
- **Documentation Leadership**: created an internal wiki, standardizing terminology and improving cross-departmental communication.
- Developed and maintained an external documentation solution (Interkassa wiki website), managing all aspects from page styling to code optimization.
- **SDLC improvements**: implemented best practices, ensuring a transparent and comprehensive feature delivery process.
- **Business Analysis:** analyzed complex datasets to identify opportunities and drive performance enhancements.
- Continuously proposed innovative solutions for improved business interaction, such as external tutorials, online merchant integration documentation, etc.

<u>Fidesint</u>. Integration consultancy – integration developer Kyiv, Ukraine

SEPTEMBER 2021 – JUNE 2022

In addition to software development, my tasks included full project lifecycle management:

- Solely responsible for the complete project lifecycle, from gathering requirements to ensuring timely delivery.
- Created intermediate documentation and clear presentations for

LANGUAGES

English: professional proficiency

Ukrainian: native speaker

Russian: native speaker Turkish: beginner

SKILLS

Product Road mapping, Agile, Scrum, Cross-functional team leadership, Strategic planning, Product development, Product design, Project Management, Customer Journey Mapping, Communication, Problemsolving, Business Analysis, SDLC, Decision-making, Jira, Confluence, Kibana, Grafana, Sentry, Google Cloud, Draw Io, Lighthouse, Git, Bitbucket, Figma, Postman

CERTIFICATES

Pro Project Management: 2023 PMP Certification Prep Course:

2023

Complete business analysis

course: 2022

Technical writing: 2022

- better communication with the customer, clarification of product requirements, and progress control.
- Managed client communication, project documentation, and coordinated the development process.
- Ensured alignment between development, stakeholders, and customer needs.
- Organized workflows and processes, ensuring optimal project execution.
- Development of schemes and diagrams to illustrate the operation of the software product.
- Structured large volumes of information.

<u>Ad Viser</u>. Financial company — *lead front-end developer*, *team lead* Kyiv, Ukraine

JUNE 2020 - OCTOBER 2021

Project Leadership & Planning:

- Oversaw planning, development, and full delivery process of multiple projects.
- Managed a small team of developers, providing mentorship and ensuring alignment with project goals.
- Developed and maintained a custom framework, streamlining application development.
- Facilitated clear communication and documentation between teams and stakeholders.

<u>Aweb Systems</u>. Marketing company — *front-end developer* Kyiv, Ukraine

JULY 2019 - FEBRUARY 2020

Software Development & Collaboration:

- Collaborated on front-end development projects, focusing on efficient and quality delivery.
- Assisted in creating documentation and communication materials, supporting overall project success.

EDUCATION

National University of 'Kyiv Mohyla Academy',

Bachelor's degree in Computer Science

Mykhailo Ostrohradskyi National University,

Master's degree in Computer Science

PM SKILLS

- Project Coordination: Proven ability in managing multifaceted projects, team collaboration, and strategic improvements.
- Technical Expertise:
 Extensive skills across
 various tools and languages.
- Technical Communication: Exceptional skills in technical communication, both in writing and speaking, with the ability to convey complex concepts clearly and effectively.
- People Skills: Strong interpersonal skills, enabling effortless communication with various stakeholders. Possesses a unique ability to understand developers, leveraging a rich technical background.